CURRICULUM VITAE



Yusuf Ali Yusuf Saleh

Personal Details:

Nationality: Bahraini

CPR No : 870600877

Civil Status: Married

Date of Birth: 19/06/1987

Phone Number: 33215323 - 32381733

Address: Bldg. 2245, Road 1946, Block 1019, Kingdom of Bahrain.

Objective:

To seek a job that suit in my education and skills which can reward both on good experience, and can develop my knowledge, if you give a chance to work on I will prove it that a good employee as to be part the team, because am working hard, Am very willing to work.

Academic Qualifications

High school (Al - Jabriya Secondary Industrial School)

Automotive Section Technician

Experience:

- Al Khunaizi Insulation Systems S.P.C 01-07-2017 To 30-09-2011
 Plumbing Electrical Maintenance Supervision
- ALHALLAG Company NOVEMBER 2011 TO JUNE 2012
 PLUMBING General Maintenance Supervision
- Alshaya Company 15-9-2012 To 13-6-2018
 Storekeeper Forklift Driver Without License
- Atlas Aluminum 7/7/2018 To 31/12/2018
 Supervision Maintenance Of Aluminum
- Brite Laundry 2/2/2019 To 30/6/2019
 Supervision Maintenance Of Machines

Courses:

- o Experiential outbound team building 25 may 2015
- o Harizons horizons hrd (for alshaya) 30 nov 2015 to 30 dec 2015
- o Harizons horizons hrd (for alshaya) 18 jon 2016 to 29feb 2016
- o Programme to aluminum Bahrain (alba) 17 spt 2005 to 13 October 2005 (Car Maintenance Section) .

Languages Know:

- Fluent in Arabic speaking, writing, and reading.
- Good in English both speaking, writing, and reading
- India speaking, writing, and reading.

Hobbies:

- Reading
- Painting
- Creative.

Personality:

- Friendly
- Loyal
- High motivate
- Working as a team.

Reference:

Available upon on request.